export const questionSchema = {
  number: 1,
  prompt: "Who is the founder of Google Developer Student Clubs PLM?",
  choices: [
    { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
    { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
    { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
    { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
  ],
  answer: "Jhepoy Dizon",
};

export const data = [
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of Google Developer Student Clubs PLM?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Neil Riego",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of Google Developer Student Clubs?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Mher Tan",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of Google Developer Student?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Jhepoy Dizon",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of Google Developer?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Miguel Mendoza",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of Google?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Miguel Mendoza",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder of?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Jhepoy Dizon",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Mher Tan",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is the founder gagagag?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Neil Riego",
  },
  {
    prompt: "the founder of Google Developer Student Clubs PLM",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Neil Riego",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who is Google Developer Student Clubs PLM?",
    choices: [
      { key: "choice-1", choice: "Neil Riego" },
      { key: "choice-2", choice: "Mher Tan" },
      { key: "choice-3", choice: "Jhepoy Dizon" },
      { key: "choice-4", choice: "Miguel Mendoza" },
    ],
    answer: "Mher Tan",
  },
];
